const PrepositionQuestion =[
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a preposition??",
        options: ["Run", "Happy  ", "Quickly", "on"],
        correct_option: "On"
      },
      {
        question: "Identify the preposition in the sentence: The book is on the table.?",
        options: ["Book", " Is  ", "On", "Table"],
        correct_option: "On"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose the correct preposition to complete the sentence: He walked ___ the park.?",
        options: ["With", "To  ", "Beautiful", "Tomorrow"],
        correct_option: "To"
      },
      {
        question: "In the sentence: She sat beside him. what is the preposition?",
        options: ["She", " Sat ", "Beside", "Him"],
        correct_option: "Beside"
      },
      {
        question: "Select the preposition from the options:?",
        options: ["Sing", " Big ", "Under", "Walk"],
        correct_option: "Under"
      },
      {
        question: "Identify the preposition in the sentence: The cat is under the table?",
        options: ["Cat", " Is ", "Under", "Table"],
        correct_option: "Udner"
      },
      {
        question: "Which word in the sentence is NOT a preposition: She danced with grace.?",
        options: ["She", " Danced ", "with", "Grace"],
        correct_option: "Grace"
      },
      {
        question: "What preposition is used in the sentence: The keys are in the drawer?",
        options: ["Are", " In ", "Key", "Drawer"],
        correct_option: "In"
      },
      {
        question: "In the sentence: He went through the tunnel. what is the preposition??",
        options: ["He", " Went ", "Through", "Tunnel"],
        correct_option: "Through"
      },
      {
        question: "Choose the correct preposition to complete the sentence: The bird flew ___ the sky.?",
        options: ["Above", "Happy  ", "Run", "Quickly"],
        correct_option: "Above"
      },
     
      




];
export default PrepositionQuestion;